[
    {
        "question": "What are the exclusions under the policy?",
        "options": [
            "Profit, loss of opportunity, loss of gain, business interruption",
            "Market loss or otherwise, or any claims arising out of loss of a pure financial nature such as loss of goodwill or any legal liability of any kind whatsoever",
            "Intentional self-injury, suicide, attempted suicide and/or the use or misuse of intoxicating drugs and/or alcohol",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the premium paying term?",
        "options": [
            "Annual",
            "Half Yearly",
            "Quarterly",
            "Monthly",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the Sum Insured options?",
        "options": [
            "Rs 50000/-",
            "Rs 100000/-",
            "Rs 150000/-",
            "Rs 200000/-",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "question": "What is the limit for Non-Medical Expenses covered by this rider?",
        "options": [
            "A fixed amount",
            "The Sum Insured of the base policy",
            "The Sum Insured of the rider",
            "A percentage of the base policy Sum Insured"
        ],
        "answer": "The Sum Insured of the chosen base policy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main benefit of opting for this cover?",
        "options": [
            "Lower premiums",
            "Higher payout for medical expenses",
            "Financial support beyond medical costs",
            "Free access to the Caringly Yours App"
        ],
        "answer": "Financial support beyond medical costs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is NOT a key feature of the Non-Medical Expenses Cover?",
        "options": [
            "Available as a rider",
            "Minimum Sum Insured of Rs. 5,00,000",
            "Covers expenses related to medical emergencies",
            "Limited by the base policy Sum Insured"
        ],
        "answer": "Covers expenses related to medical emergencies"
    },
    {
        "question": "How can you download the 'Caringly Yours' app?",
        "options": [
            "Visit the Bajaj website",
            "Scan the QR code provided",
            "Call the Bajaj helpline",
            "Download from the App Store or Google Play"
        ],
        "answer": "Scan the QR code provided"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Non-Medical Expenses Cover?",
        "options": [
            "To reduce insurance premiums",
            "To provide coverage for medical emergencies",
            "To offer additional financial protection beyond medical costs",
            "To replace the base health insurance policy"
        ],
        "answer": "To offer additional financial protection beyond medical costs"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the suggested action for potential customers?",
        "options": [
            "Contact a Bajaj agent",
            "Visit the Bajaj website",
            "Download the Caringly Yours App",
            "Upgrade their existing policy"
        ],
        "answer": "Upgrade their existing policy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the likely target audience for this insurance product?",
        "options": [
            "Young adults with no dependents",
            "People with pre-existing medical conditions",
            "Individuals seeking comprehensive financial protection",
            "Businesses with large employee groups"
        ],
        "answer": "Individuals seeking comprehensive financial protection"
=======
        "question": "What are the detail coverages under the policy?",
        "options": [
            "Critical Illness Cover",
            "Congenital Disability Benefit",
            "Children Education Bonus Benefit",
            "Loss of Job",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the advantages of this policy?",
        "options": [
            "The insured receives the amount as lump sum so that he can plan the treatment accordingly",
            "Additional benefits like coverage for new born baby's congenital ailments, Children education bonus, Loss of job are available under same policy",
            "Hassel free in-house claim process",
            "Premium paid is exempt under section 80-D of Income Tax Act",
            "Very competitive premium rates",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the entry age?",
        "options": [
            "21 yrs \u2013 65yrs",
            "18 yrs \u2013 65yrs",
            "25 yrs \u2013 65yrs",
            "18 yrs \u2013 70yrs"
        ],
        "answer": "21 yrs \u2013 65yrs"
    },
    {
        "question": "What will be the renewal age?",
        "options": [
            "Lifetime renewal benefit is available under the policy except on the grounds of fraud, misrepresentation or moral hazard",
            "Upto 70 years",
            "Upto 75 years",
            "Upto 80 years"
        ],
        "answer": "Lifetime renewal benefit is available under the policy except on the grounds of fraud, misrepresentation or moral hazard"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Pre policy Medical examination criteria?",
        "options": [
            "Pre policy medical examination mandatory for age 41years and above the purpose of waiting period",
            "Pre policy medical examination mandatory for age 35years and above the purpose of waiting period",
            "Pre policy medical examination mandatory for age 45years and above the purpose of waiting period",
            "Pre policy medical examination mandatory for age 50years and above the purpose of waiting period"
        ],
        "answer": "Pre policy medical examination mandatory for age 41years and above the purpose of waiting period"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the policy period?",
        "options": [
            "1 year",
            "2 years",
            "3 years",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "When can I enhance my Sum Insured under this policy?",
        "options": [
            "At the time of renewal, by submitting a fresh proposal form and renewal notice to the company",
            "Only when there's a claim",
            "Only on the anniversary date of the policy",
            "Never"
        ],
        "answer": "At the time of renewal, by submitting a fresh proposal form and renewal notice to the company"
>>>>>>> ab756e686332b9cb5b09fbd52626638cb4dc3bb9
    }
]